If you want to give a 15-day break, then look at this. I'm definitely
listening because there are a
lot of option participants and
activists, and as you said,
after the opening in the valley, it's at 20 rupees a kilo.
But my own guess is that it might
even open at 100 rupees. But in the coming days,
it will be seen going up because the
harvest this time will be less because
in the Holland plantations, it has been said
that work will start in the plantations, but
due to social distancing, everything will be at a lower level.
And I think that the production from there will be
less, so because of this, the
demand will be increased, the supply will be less, due to which the
tea will see a rise in the coming
days. Now, if I talk about any stock, as
Ahmed also said just now, there is
not much money invested in it, that's
why other companies or whatever,
they
are fine from a trading perspective, but if someone is investing
and now starts keeping a long-term portfolio, then
I think there is only one
stock which completely meets the criteria
and that is your Tata Group.
Considering the prices that are coming not only on tea but also on coffee, mineral water and even up to Dow Chemicals, I feel that it will emerge as a very big
company and
if it is done on a similar level of vibrations with other film related companies, then
that choice is very reasonable. I
think one should buy here once,
this stock can definitely give a return of at least 15 to 20 percent in a year.